/*SAMPLE DECK OF CARDS since I don't have a db atm*/

module.exports = [

	{question : 'English1', answer : 'Korean1'}, 
	{question : 'English2', answer : 'Korean2'}, 
	{question : 'English3', answer : 'Korean3'}, 
	{question : 'English4', answer : 'Korean4'}, 
	{question : 'English5', answer : 'Korean5'},

	{question : 'English6', answer : 'Korean6'}, 
	{question : 'English7', answer : 'Korean7'}, 
	{question : 'English8', answer : 'Korean8'}, 
	{question : 'English9', answer : 'Korean9'}, 
	{question : 'English10', answer : 'Korean10'},

	{question : 'English11', answer : 'Korean11'}, 
	{question : 'English12', answer : 'Korean12'}, 
	{question : 'English13', answer : 'Korean13'}, 
	{question : 'English14', answer : 'Korean14'}, 
	{question : 'English15', answer : 'Korean15'},

	{question : 'English16', answer : 'Korean16'}, 
	{question : 'English17', answer : 'Korean17'}, 
	{question : 'English18', answer : 'Korean18'}, 
	{question : 'English19', answer : 'Korean19'}, 
	{question : 'English20', answer : 'Korean20'},

	{question : 'English21', answer : 'Korean21'}, 
	{question : 'English22', answer : 'Korean22'}, 
	{question : 'English23', answer : 'Korean23'}, 
	{question : 'English24', answer : 'Korean24'}, 
	{question : 'English25', answer : 'Korean25'},

	{question : 'English26', answer : 'Korean26'}, 
	{question : 'English27', answer : 'Korean27'}, 
	{question : 'English28', answer : 'Korean28'}, 
	{question : 'English29', answer : 'Korean29'}, 
	{question : 'English30', answer : 'Korean30'},

	{question : 'English31', answer : 'Korean31'}, 
	{question : 'English32', answer : 'Korean32'}, 
	{question : 'English33', answer : 'Korean33'}, 
	{question : 'English34', answer : 'Korean34'}, 
	{question : 'English35', answer : 'Korean35'},

	{question : 'English36', answer : 'Korean36'}, 
	{question : 'English37', answer : 'Korean37'}, 
	{question : 'English38', answer : 'Korean38'}, 
	{question : 'English39', answer : 'Korean39'}, 
	{question : 'English40', answer : 'Korean40'},

	{question : 'English41', answer : 'Korean41'}, 
	{question : 'English42', answer : 'Korean42'}, 
	{question : 'English43', answer : 'Korean43'}, 
	{question : 'English44', answer : 'Korean44'}, 
	{question : 'English45', answer : 'Korean45'},

	{question : 'English46', answer : 'Korean46'}, 
	{question : 'English47', answer : 'Korean47'}, 
	{question : 'English48', answer : 'Korean48'}, 
	{question : 'English49', answer : 'Korean49'}, 
	{question : 'English50', answer : 'Korean50'},

	{question : 'English51', answer : 'Korean51'}, 
	{question : 'English52', answer : 'Korean52'}, 
	{question : 'English53', answer : 'Korean53'}, 
	{question : 'English54', answer : 'Korean54'}, 
	{question : 'English55', answer : 'Korean55'},

	{question : 'English56', answer : 'Korean56'}, 
	{question : 'English57', answer : 'Korean57'}, 
	{question : 'English58', answer : 'Korean58'}, 
	{question : 'English59', answer : 'Korean59'}, 
	{question : 'English60', answer : 'Korean60'},

	{question : 'English61', answer : 'Korean61'}, 
	{question : 'English62', answer : 'Korean62'}, 
	{question : 'English63', answer : 'Korean63'}, 
	{question : 'English64', answer : 'Korean64'}, 
	{question : 'English65', answer : 'Korean65'},

	{question : 'English66', answer : 'Korean66'}, 
	{question : 'English67', answer : 'Korean67'}, 
	{question : 'English68', answer : 'Korean68'}, 
	{question : 'English69', answer : 'Korean69'}, 
	{question : 'English70', answer : 'Korean70'},

	{question : 'English71', answer : 'Korean71'}, 
	{question : 'English72', answer : 'Korean72'}, 
	{question : 'English73', answer : 'Korean73'}, 
	{question : 'English74', answer : 'Korean74'}, 
	{question : 'English75', answer : 'Korean75'},

	{question : 'English76', answer : 'Korean76'}, 
	{question : 'English77', answer : 'Korean77'}, 
	{question : 'English78', answer : 'Korean78'}, 
	{question : 'English79', answer : 'Korean79'}, 
	{question : 'English80', answer : 'Korean80'},

	{question : 'English81', answer : 'Korean81'}, 
	{question : 'English82', answer : 'Korean82'}, 
	{question : 'English83', answer : 'Korean83'}, 
	{question : 'English84', answer : 'Korean84'}, 
	{question : 'English85', answer : 'Korean85'},

	{question : 'English86', answer : 'Korean86'}, 
	{question : 'English87', answer : 'Korean87'}, 
	{question : 'English88', answer : 'Korean88'}, 
	{question : 'English89', answer : 'Korean89'}, 
	{question : 'English90', answer : 'Korean90'},

	{question : 'English91', answer : 'Korean91'}, 
	{question : 'English92', answer : 'Korean92'}, 
	{question : 'English93', answer : 'Korean93'}, 
	{question : 'English94', answer : 'Korean94'}, 
	{question : 'English95', answer : 'Korean95'},

	{question : 'English96', answer : 'Korean96'}, 
	{question : 'English97', answer : 'Korean97'}, 
	{question : 'English98', answer : 'Korean98'}, 
	{question : 'English99', answer : 'Korean99'}, 
	{question : 'English100', answer : 'Korean100'},

	{question : 'English101', answer : 'Korean101'}, 
	{question : 'English102', answer : 'Korean102'}, 
	{question : 'English103', answer : 'Korean103'}, 
	{question : 'English104', answer : 'Korean104'}, 
	{question : 'English105', answer : 'Korean105'},

	{question : 'English106', answer : 'Korean106'}, 
	{question : 'English107', answer : 'Korean107'}, 
	{question : 'English108', answer : 'Korean108'}, 
	{question : 'English109', answer : 'Korean109'}, 
	{question : 'English110', answer : 'Korean110'},

	{question : 'English111', answer : 'Korean111'}, 
	{question : 'English112', answer : 'Korean112'}, 
	{question : 'English113', answer : 'Korean113'}, 
	{question : 'English114', answer : 'Korean114'}, 
	{question : 'English115', answer : 'Korean115'},

	{question : 'English116', answer : 'Korean116'}, 
	{question : 'English117', answer : 'Korean117'}, 
	{question : 'English118', answer : 'Korean118'}, 
	{question : 'English119', answer : 'Korean119'}, 
	{question : 'English120', answer : 'Korean120'},

	{question : 'English121', answer : 'Korean121'}, 
	{question : 'English122', answer : 'Korean122'}, 
	{question : 'English123', answer : 'Korean123'}, 
	{question : 'English124', answer : 'Korean124'}, 
	{question : 'English125', answer : 'Korean125'}

];